browzit.com 2017-05-22

# Privacy policy for website

## PRIVACY POLICY FOR WEBSITE

### OVERVIEW

We value your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. 

In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe the information that we collect from visitors to and users of our websites (“Sites”), our blogs, our Applications, and our online products and services (collectively, “Services”). By visiting our Sites or using any of our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND WHY?

The information we collect from you allows you to log into our Sites; use our Services and Applications; and register for and/or set up registration for you or your organization’s own customers for our services/products/activities (collectively, “Events”). We also collect information from businesses, organizations, and individuals who request information from us.

Individuals and agents of individuals may provide us information directly or indirectly by registering for an Event or by otherwise using our Services (these individuals are referred to as “Consumers”). For example, you may enter your information in order to register for an Event, or someone may enter your information on your behalf to register for the Event. In addition, individuals or organizations can use our Services to set up Events for Consumers (those who use our Services to provide a service to Consumers are referred to as “Clients”). Relatedly, our Clients (including agents of our Clients) may provide us personal information about consumers who have registered for an Event being operated by our Client or who the Client wants us to contact or otherwise provide Services to on behalf of the Client.

### Information We Collect Directly From You. 

Account Information for our Sites. You may browse our Sites without creating an online account or providing us with your information, but to use certain features or to register for an Event, you may need to create an account or otherwise provide us with information. When you create an account with us or register for an Event, we may ask you to provide the following:

  *  Your first and last name;
  * Your email address and your desired password;
  * Your display name (this is the name other people will see when you post items to one of our Sites or engage in other similar activities on our site);
  * Your date of birth;
  * Your subscription preferences (whether and what types of information you would like us to send you)
  * Information about your activities and interests;
  * Other profile data, such as contact information, occupation, gender and photo;
  * Your physical activities or similar health related information (how long you exercised, caloric intake or weight lost);
  * The contact of information of a friend (when inviting them to visit the Site);
  * Payment information, such as credit card or financial account numbers (if applicable).
  * Medical details such as medical aid information in the event of an emergency.

Log in Information for our Sites. Once you have signed up for our Site, on subsequent visits to our Site, you may simply need to enter your user ID or email address (as applicable) and password to gain access to the Site.

Contests, Surveys and Questionnaires. When you sign up for sweepstakes or contests, or complete questionnaires or surveys, we collect the information you submit to us. We use this information to administer the sweepstakes, contest or survey, to analyze the results, for research purposes, to send you other information or offers we think may be of interest to you, to comply with legal requirements, and for other purposes as discussed in this Policy. 

User Profiles, Comments and Posts. Some of our Sites and Applications allow users to create or post content, such as comments, profiles, blogs, and messages. If you provide content to our Sites, we may collect and use that information as described in this Policy. Please note that such information may be viewed, collected or used by other registered users and public visitors to our Sites. Once posted, we cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law or your personal privacy. Your profile, however, may offer privacy settings within your account to help you manage how your content is displayed.

Information We Collect from Facebook. We may provide you with the opportunity to connect via Facebook, through our Sites or Applications. For example, you can indicate that you are going to participate in an Event and invite your Facebook friends to join that Event. If you log into Facebook through our Sites or Applications, we will request permission to (i) access your basic information, which includes your name, profile picture, gender, networks, Facebook user ID, list of friends and any other information that you have made public on Facebook; and (ii) manage your participation in Events (so that we may RSVP on your behalf). For information about how Facebook may disclose your information, including any information you make public, please consult the Facebook Data Use Policy. We have no control over how Facebook uses or discloses the personal information you provide to it. We store the information that we receive from Facebook along with other information that we collect from you or receive about you.

Information We Collect About You From Third Parties. We also may collect information, including personally identifiable information, about you from our affiliates and non-affiliated third parties. 

Information We Collect Automatically. We may use cookies, web beacons, and other automated devices to collect information, including personally identifiable information, about you when you visit our Sites and receive emails from us. Specifically, we may collect the following information about your use of our Sites via these technologies: your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address; your approximate geographic location; your interaction with the Sites; length of time you are logged in to our Sites; and websites visited before or after our Sites. In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the website. When Customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our Site. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages. We also collect non-personal data (including, without limitation, of the type set forth above) from third parties. The information we collect from third parties may be combined with the information we collect. This information also may be associated with your username and combined with other information, including personally identifiable information that we collect about you. 

### HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

We may use the information that we gather about you for the following purposes: 

  * To provide our Services to you, to communicate with you about your use of our Services and for other customer service purposes;
  * To provide information that you have requested to receive from us in response to your opt-in requests;
  * To provide our Services at the request of our Clients;
  * To administer Events;
  * To improve our Sites and Services by providing personalized experiences, location customization, personalized help, and instructions;
  * For marketing and advertising purposes; for example, we may use your information to display targeted advertisements to you on our Sites and to assist us in advertising our Services on third party websites;
  * To send you email, follow-up questions about your Event or your participation in an Event, news and newsletters, promotions, and/or invitations to visit the Site;
  * To better understand how users access and use our Sites and Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, and for other research purposes.

Clients should note that we may use information we receive or collect regarding Consumers (including without limitation via an Event registration page) in accordance with the terms of this Policy, including in the manner set forth above. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in certain contexts, we collect information on behalf of our Clients subject to contractual requirements that limit our ability to use and transfer your information in ways that are more narrow than those in this Policy (e.g., the information be only used as necessary to provide Services to the Client and/or for other specified purposes). In those limited circumstances, your information is subject to those contractual requirements and not to this Policy, subject to enforcement by the applicable Client. If your information is collected on behalf of a third party, it will be evident at the time that you provide such information. This Policy does not cover our Clients’ use of your information outside of our Services. You should contact that party directly to determine if your information is subject to such limitations on uses and to ascertain how the third party will make use of your information.

### WHEN AND HOW DO SHARE INFORMATION IT RECEIVES? 

**Third Parties/International Organization.** We may share your information, including personally identifiable information, with non-affiliated and affiliated third parties. 

**Affiliates** : We may disclose the information we collect from you to our affiliates or subsidiaries; however, if we do so, their use and disclosure of your information will be subject to this Policy.

**Event Sponsors or Partners:**  If you are using our Services to register for an Event or to purchase a third party product or service, We share the personal information that you provide with the applicable third parties in order to fulfil your request. 

**Service Providers** : We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents who perform functions on our behalf. For example, these providers may help us administer our Sites and Applications manage and administer Events, or process credit card payments. These third parties have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of or information and may be located wherever we operates. Where required by law, these companies agree to only use such information for the purposes for which they have been engaged by us unless you expressly permit them to use your information for other purposes. 

**Other Non-Affiliated Third Parties:** We may disclose the information that we collect about you to non-affiliated third parties (with your consent, if consent is required by law), such as promotional partners and others with whom we have marketing or other relationships. Those third parties may use your information for marketing purposes, such as to market products and services that they believe would be of interest to you. We also may combine the information that we collect about you with other information that we obtain from third parties. This information may help us to determine what advertisements to direct to you, to place on our website, and where to advertise our Services. As discussed in the advertising section below, you have the ability to opt out of certain uses of your information. You also have the ability to opt in to receiving certain information from us and non-affiliated third parties.

**Supplemental Service Partners:** By purchasing, making reservations or registering for, products or services offered by third parties as a result of your interaction with the Services or use of the Sites, electing to receive communications (such as emails), offered or sponsored by third parties on the Site, you consent to our providing your personal information to those third parties, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Those third parties may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact those third parties to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that we will have the right to use and disclose all such information submitted by you to such third parties in the same manner in which we have the right to use and disclose all other information submitted by you directly to us.

We also may share your information for the following reasons: 

  * In Response to Legal Process. We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal process, such as in response to a subpoena.
  * To Protect us and Others(Public interest). We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy. 

**Third Party Applications**. Third party applications, such as the Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, or Google buttons, may be available on our Sites. The owners or providers of those third party applications may collect personally identifiable information from you. Their collection of information is bound by their own information collection policies and practices. Your interactions with third party applications on our Sites may be shared with others within your social network. We are not responsible for the collection and use of your information by third parties.

**Network Advertisers.** Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Sites and other websites you have visited. This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. These third party services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third party technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third parties with information, including both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information, about your usage of our Sites and our Services. 

**Third Party Links.** At times, our Sites and Applications may contain links to other third party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but, instead, is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites, and we are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites. 

### HOW SECURE IS INFORMATION ABOUT ME?

We have implemented commercially reasonable precautions, including, where appropriate, password protection, encryption, and secure socket layering to protect our Sites and the information we collect from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security all of the time. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any of your personal information via the Internet.

You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, computer, and web-enabled devices, among other things, by signing off after using a shared computer, inserting a password on your web-enabled device, choosing a password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, keeping your password private, and periodically changing your password. You should never share your log-in information with others. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen or compromised passwords, or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.

### CAN I ACCESS AND MODIFY MY PERSONAL INFORMATION? 

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/remove, or ask to have it removed from a public forum or testimonial by making the change within your account settings or by contacting us via one of the methods listed in this Policy. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days and may charge a prescribed fee as communicated to you prior to the release of the personal information.  Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified, or deleted may continue to reside in our systems for a period of time. Also, you may not be able to remove your personal information from archived web pages that we no longer maintain In the event we are unable to complete your access request, we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law.

If your information has been shared with a third party, as described above, or collected on behalf of a Client, then that third party has received their own copy of your data. If you have been contacted by one of these third parties, or one of our Clients, and wish to correct or request they delete your information, please contact them directly. 

### CHILDREN UNDER 18

Parents/guardians/competent persons (“Parents”) have the right to consent to the collection and use of personal information from children under the age of 18 (collectively, “Children,” and individually, a “Child”) without also consenting to the disclosure of such information to outside third parties, except in order to provide the Services. We do not share personal information collected from Children with third parties for any purpose other than to provide the Services.

**What information do we collect from children under the age of 18?**

  * Personal information such as a parent’s/child’s email address;
  * Username and password;
  * Date of birth;
  * Display name (this is the name other people will see when the Child posts items to one of our Sites or engage in other similar activities on our Sites);
  * Information about a Child’s activities and interests;
  * Other profile data, such as contact information, gender, and photo (collected from the parent);
  * Physical activities or similar health related information. 

**How we use the information collected from Children?**

  * To provide a notice to parents regarding your Child’s interest in registering to use the Sites;
  * To obtain verifiable parental consent;
  * To provide our Services, to communicate with parents about your Child’s use of our Services and for other customer service purposes;
  * To provide information that a parent or Child has requested to receive from us in response to an opt-in request;
  * To provide our Services at the request of our Clients
  * To administer Events;
  * To improve our Sites and Services by providing personalized experiences, location customization, personalized help, and instructions.

If your Child’s personal information changes, if you no longer wish to allow your Child to participate on the Sites, or if you wish to delete your Child’s information and refuse further collection and use of the information, please email us 

**How long is my Child’s information retained?**

We will retain the information we collect for as long as your or your Child’s account is active, as needed to provide our Services. You may close your or your Child’s account by contacting us. Nonetheless, we may retain your or your Child’s information for an additional period as is permitted or required to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and for historical, statistical or research purposes. Please note that even if we delete your or your Child’s information, it may persist on backup or archival media and other information systems. 

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may change this Policy from time to time, so be sure to check back periodically. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to notify you in advance of such change, by highlighting the change on the Sites or by sending an email to you at the email address that you have registered with us. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Policy will indicate your agreement with the terms of the revised Policy.

If we make material changes to how we use personal information collected from Children under age 18, we will notify parents by email (at the address provided to us) in order to obtain verifiable parental consent for the new uses of the Child's personal information.

### CONTACT US

Address:  

All enquiries must be addressed to the information officer.

### DISPUTES

You have the right at any time to rectify the Personal Information collected, object to the processing of Personal Information(subject to legislation) and to lodge a complaint at the Information Regulator with contact details.
